<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Help Message -->
    <string name="help_message">Travel Blog is an app for creating posts tagged with location and timestamp.\n
On the web: the full <a href="https://code.google.com/p/travel-blog-android/wiki/UserGuide">User Guide</a>.\n
\n
Setup:\n
Make sure Location Access is turned on on your Android device settings.
For best performance, turn on both GPS Satellites and Wi-Fi and Mobile networks.\n
\n
The <b>New Trip</b> menu command starts a new trip. This will be the KML filename of the blog (located in /TravelBlog/ on your SD card).\n
Click on <b>New Post</b> when you want to log your location.
This brings up a new page where you can type a name and description.  While you are typing, it finds your location.
If you need to modify the location, you can later edit the location on a map.\n
\n
You can <b>edit a post</b> by clicking on it, and you can <b>delete a post</b> by long-clicking on a post and selecting the delete command.
When editing you a given the opportunity to edit the name and description,
and optionally to edit the location of your post by clicking on the location coordinates.\n
\n
You can view your trip on a Google map on your device by choosing <b>Map Trip</b> from the menu.
You can copy the KML blog file manually to do what you choose with it, or you can send it via email
or wherever your device can send it to by choosing Send Trip from the menu.\n
\n
What works well for us is to install the Android Dropbox app, register with Dropbox, and then Send the KML file to your Dropbox public folder.
In Dropbox you can get a link to your file which you can enter into the Search Maps box in Google Maps.
This works from either the desktop Google Maps, or the mobile Google Maps app.  You can then share this map with friends,
or add it to your favourite Blogging website such as Blogger.
This way, your family, friends or colleagues can also know what you are up to.\n
\n
Later you can Open Trip to load old trips, or select new Trip again to start again.  Your last Trip is also loaded on start-up.  Nothing runs in the background.\n
\n
Happy travelling!\n
\n
The Travel Blog Team</string>

    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    
    <!--  About Message -->
    <string name="about_message">Travel Blog location app<br/>\n
<a href="https://code.google.com/p/travel-blog-android/">Source Code and Docs</a>\n
<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.barkside.travellocblog">Google Play Store</a>\n
Copyright 2011 Barkside Apps</string>

    <!--  What's New Message -->
    <string name="whatsnew_message"><b>What\'s New</b>\n
\n
<b>Version 2.0.1</b>\n
* Locations are now editable using a map.
When editing a post, click on location text to bring up a map.\n
\n
* Clicking on blog entry in the main list now invokes the post editing screen.\n
\n
* Settings menu added for customizing app behavior.\n
\n
<b>Version 1.7</b>\n
* App is now open source.\n
\n</string>

    <string name="whatsnew_title">What\'s New</string>
        
</resources>
